<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BHF Donate</string>

    <string name="bt_submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="title_activity_list_item">Item List</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="suggested_price">Suggested Price</string>
    <string name="title_activity_profile">My Profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gift_aid_signup">GiftAidSignupActivity</string>

    <string name="coronary"><![CDATA[<p>Coronary heart disease(CHD), is the leading cause of death both in the UK and
worldwide. Each year, about 1 in 6 men and 1 in 10 women in the UK die from CHD.
CHD is caused by the build up of fatty material inside the artery walls. This
build up of fat narrows the artery walls and may cause a blood clot to form.
If it blocks the coronary artery and cuts off the supply of oxygen-rich
blood to your heart muscle, your heart may become permanently damanged. This is
known as a heart attack.
Learn more: <a href="http://tinyurl.com/prbsx65">http://tinyurl.com/prbsx65</a>
<p>]]></string>

    <string name="inherited"><![CDATA[<p>Inherited conditions can be passed on through families. They can affect many parts
of the body or cause many different conditions and are sometimes called genetic
heart conditions.
Inherited heart conditions can cause heart rhythm disturbances, cardiomyopathies
(enlarged heart) and very high cholesterol levels. These conditions can lead to
strokes, heart failure and heart attacks.
Learn more: <a href="http://tinyurl.com/zjunaq9">http://tinyurl.com/zjunaq9</a>
<p>]]></string>

    <string name="regenerative"><![CDATA[<p>In 2013 we took a major step towards mending broken hearts when we committed to
funding four pioneering Centres of Regenerative Medicine at top UK universities.
The universities involved are working on finding ways to grow new blood vessels
to replace those damanged by a heart attack, developing ways to grow patches of
heart tissue from stem cells that could be used to repair damaged hearts and
understanding how the heart might be taught to repair itself after the damage
of a heart attack.
Learn more: <a href="http://tinyurl.com/z8y476r">http://tinyurl.com/z8y476r</a>
<p>]]></string>

    <string name="atrial"><![CDATA[<p>An irregular pulse could be a sign that you have an abnormal heart rhythm.
Atrial Fibrillation (AF) is one of the most common forms of abnormal heart rhythm
and it is a major cause of strokes.
AF can be inherited from birth but it can also be linked to come from high blood
pressure, heart valve disease, overactive thyroid gland and excessive alcohol
consumption.
Learn more: <a href="http://tinyurl.com/zw96qwc">http://tinyurl.com/zw96qwc</a>
<p>]]></string>

    <string name="cardiomyopathy"><![CDATA[<p>Cardiomyopathy is a disease of the heart muscle. It can run in families and can
affect one or several members of a family. Some members of a family may be
affected more than others and some family members may not be affected or have any
symptons at all.
Cardiomyopathy changes the size of your heart and can also affect the way the
electrical system makes your heart beat.
Learn more: <a href="http://tinyurl.com/m2639pb">http://tinyurl.com/m2639pb</a>
<p>]]></string>

    <string name="septic"><![CDATA[<p>Sepsis is a life-threatening condition caused by infection and it leads to more
than 100,000 people being admitted to UK hospitals every year. Around 37% of
those admitted to hospital die in hospital.
The BHF is funding research into L-257 a revelutionary new drug which, if
development progresses at its current rate will be a drug in circulaation
mid 2017
successful, will be in production in 2017.
<p>]]></string>
    <string name="title_activity_research_detail">Research Detail</string>
</resources>
